teksystems.com 2017-04-20

# Allegis Group Privacy Policy

## Allegis Group Online Privacy Statement

_Effective Date: 2017_

Allegis Group and its group companies, click here, (collectively, " **Allegis Group** ", or " **we"** ) are committed to safeguarding your privacy. In this Privacy & Cookie Policy (" **Policy** ") we explain to you what information we may collect, use, share and store about you, and the choices and rights that are available to you.  If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us using the contact details provided below. 

We participate in and comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Economic Area (" **EEA** ") member countries and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. You can find out more about our Privacy Shield commitment's below, click here.

## About Allegis Group

##  

Through our network of specialized operating companies, Allegis Group partners with organizations across the globe to optimize talent attraction and retention— while simultaneously providing individuals with significant opportunities to realize their professional aspirations and achieve personal success.  We partner with clients to help them achieve their talent strategies and business goals, and we partner with potential candidates about their career aspirations.  

Using our industry expertise we’ve developed a full suite of talent solutions — from talent acquisition services to fully-outsourced workforce management offerings.  To learn more about the details of our services offerings, please click here.

• Staffing and recruiting services for technical, professional, and industrial positions through Aerotek, as well as managed engineering services via EASi.

• Staffing and recruiting services for risk and compliance, operations, business and organizational change, finance, and management consultancy positions via Aston Carter.

• Legal search, recruiting, and flexible workforce services for lawyers and legal professionals through Major, Lindsey & Africa and MLA-Solutions Practice Group.

• Executive search services across an entire organization, including board of directors, C-suite, executive and senior VPs, and directors through Allegis Partners.

• An online job board and resource for job seekers with disabilities and employers looking to hire in the U.S. via Getting Hired.

• IT staffing solutions, IT talent management expertise, as well as managed, project-based, and outsourced IT services via TEKsystems Global Services

• A proven alternative to outsourced sales, providing customized sales solutions for retail and B2B customers through MarketSource.

• Permanent and contingent workforce management solutions, talent advisory services, and integrated talent solutions through Allegis Global Solutions.

## When this Policy Applies

This Policy applies to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information:

(i)       through our website(s) and related applications and content that link or refer to this Policy (including the Allegis Group websites listed here: Allegis Group websites); and Allegis computer or mobile software applications (“ **apps** ”) and content made available to you) (collectively the “ **Sites** ”); 

(ii)      in connection with any of our events or sales, marketing, advertising and recruitment activities or in the course of providing other Allegis Group services to you (collectively with the Sites, the " **Allegis Services** "); and

(iii)      when receiving services from you.

This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of third parties that Allegis Group does not own or control.

Back to the Top

**What is in this Policy?**

_Click on one of the links below to jump to a specific section:_

_Collection of Personal Information  
Use of Personal Information  
Cookies and Online Tracking  
Sharing Your Personal Information within Allegis  
Sharing Your Personal Information with Third Parties  
International Data Transfers  
EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework  
Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework Safe Harbor Framework  
Your Privacy Rights  
Security of Your Personal Information  
Children’s Privacy  
Links to Other Sites and Public Forums  
Contacting Us  
Changes to this Policy  
Additional Notices  
Additional Information That Applies to MarketSource Customers_

## Collection of Personal Information

Allegis Group collects and maintains personal information from the following categories of individuals:

  * **Visitors:** individuals who visit or use our Site(s) or any other Allegis Services, so that we can provide them with the Site(s) or Allegis Services they require;

  * **Job seekers** : individuals that apply for job opportunities with Allegis Group to fill our internal positions or as part of our staffing and recruiting services or Allegis Group’s customers through our search, workforce management or talent advisory services (in each case, whether such applications are made online or offline) **;**

  * **Customers, vendors, service providers and other suppliers** : employees, representatives and/or agents of our customers, service providers, vendors and other suppliers with whom we have a business relationship and/or manage on behalf of our customers. 

If you submit any personal information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the Allegis Services, you confirm that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Policy. 

**The types of information we collect include the following:**

  * **Information submitted to us:** Allegis Group collects personal information that individuals provide to us through Allegis Services, such as when they visit one of our Sites, post on our forums or blogs, sign up for an Allegis account to access certain Allegis Services (like an Allegis Group job board or our Communities Site) or if they subscribe to our marketing or register for an Allegis Group event or webinar or otherwise contact us.  We may also collect personal information from individuals’ offline, for example when individuals provide information to us by telephone or in person at events or at one of our recruitment offices.   

The types of personal information we may collect include:

    * contact information (such as name, postal address, email address and telephone number); 

    * username and password when you register on our Sites; 

    * professional information, such as your job title, department or job role; 

    * information you provide about others you would like us to contact (for example referrals or references) or information regarding your emergency contacts; 

    * resume or C.V. information, such as employment and education history, language proficiencies, security clearance information and other work-related skills, awards and honors, membership in clubs and organizations, personal interests and activities and information regarding your career interests and other qualifications for or desires regarding future employment opportunities, including information regarding desired compensation and benefits; and 

    * citizenship and work authorization status.  

Where we request information from you, we will let you know prior to collection whether the provision of the personal information we are requesting is compulsory or whether the information may be provided on a voluntary basis and the consequences of not providing the information.  ** **

  * **Information we collect automatically:** We automatically collect certain technical information from visitors to our Site(s), such as the Internet protocol (IP) address of their device, their login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platforms.  We may also automatically collect certain information about their visits to our Site(s), such as download errors experienced and length of visits to certain pages. When you download, install or use Allegis Group apps, we and our service providers may track and collect certain device related information (such as your device's unique ID) and certain app usage data (such as the date and time the app on your device accesses our servers and what information and files have been downloaded to the app based on your device ID. 

  * **Information we receive from other sources or third parties:**  We may receive or acquire information about our visitors, job seekers, customers and suppliers from third party partners (such as background check providers) or other third party sources (such as information from publically available sites (like Monster.com, CareerBuilder.com or LinkedIn)),or a job seeker’s third party reference.  

  * You may also choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by third parties like social media sites.  For example, if you register for an account to access some of our Sites (like the Communities Site), you can choose to import your LinkedIn basic profile data (such as your name, experience, location, photo and contact information). By authorizing Allegis Group to have access to this information, you agree that we may collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

** Sensitive Personal Information: **In connection with the various services we provide or if you are applying for a job opportunity with us or one of our customers, you may be asked  for types of  personal information that are viewed by some countries as sensitive personal information. Sensitive personal information includes, for example, government-issued  identification number (such as  a social security number), information relating to a person's race or ethnic origin, political opinions or religious beliefs, physical or mental health or  condition, sexual orientation, trade union  membership, genetic data and any related legal actions or the processing of biometric data for the purposes of uniquely identifying an  individual.  It also includes information about an individual's  criminal offences or convictions, as well as any other information deemed sensitive under applicable data protection  laws (collectively **"Sensitive Personal Information").  **

  * Although we aim to minimize the amount of Sensitive Personal Information we process, we may process such information in certain circumstances, such as where we are required to or permitted to do so by law (e.g. information about your racial / ethnic origin, gender and disabilities for equal opportunity monitoring or affirmative action program), or where it is necessary to provide you with a service, or if we need to perform a criminal background check, drug/alcohol test or fitness for duty testing.  If required by applicable data protection laws, we will obtain your express consent to our use of your sensitive personal information. .

## Use of Personal Information

The personal information Allegis Group collects will be used only as described in this Policy and/or in the way we specify at the time of collection.  For the most part, we collect and use personal information to effectively provide and improve the Allegis Services (such as our Sites and related staffing and recruiting services, or search, workforce management or talent advisory services)  and to comply with applicable laws and government regulations (such as,  to comply with mandatory employment, tax and insurance requirements). 

More specifically, we may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * Providing  and administering the Allegis Services and for internal operations (for example, troubleshooting, data analysis, statistical and survey purposes); 
  * Protecting the Allegis Services (for example, fraud monitoring and prevention); 
  * Responding to your communications;  
  * Complying with applicable laws and government regulations; 
  * If you are a job seeker: 
    * facilitating the recruitment, staffing or search process by helping to find job seekers a suitable assignment or job match with us or with our customers; 
    * storing information about your recruitment or other preferences; 
    * sending you e-mails and other communications about job postings that we think fit your profile, and to notify you about events, surveys, workshops and training sessions run by Allegis Group; and 
    * to interact with you on third party social networks (like LinkedIn). 
  * Gauging the number of users and usage of the Site(s), so we can plan Site bandwidth and capacity accordingly; 
  * Recognizing you when you return as a repeat visitor to our Site(s) or other online Allegis Services; 
  * Providing information on goods and services you have requested; 
  * Sending you e-mails and other promotional communications about Allegis Group marketing, advertising and promotions in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt-out of our marketing at any time (see "Your Choices" below); 
  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, services and offerings, enhancing, improving or modifying our Sites, products and services and operating and expanding our business activities; and

  * Notifying you about changes to our Site(s) or other Allegis Services.

Personal information collected online through the Allegis Services may also be supplemented with information you provide to us through other Allegis Group services , as well as other online and offline sources (such as recruitment fairs, social media platforms (like LinkedIn), trade shows, or other events) and other data appending methods (such as spot tags, tracking and cookies as referenced below).

We may also use the personal information we receive for the purposes of creating anonymized and aggregated statistics that do not reveal the specific identity of any person.

In most cases, Allegis Group will process personal information for a variety of business purposes which are in our  legitimate interests (for example, to operate its business and provide you with services you have requested), in order to enter into or perform a contract with youand/or for compliance with our legal obligations (as described above). However in some cases and always where required by applicable law, Allegis Group will seek your consent to process your personal information (including any Sensitive Personal Information).  

Back to the Top

## Cookies and Online Tracking

Allegis Group websites use "cookies" and similar technologies (like web bugs) to help personalize your online experience and for our analytics purposes. 

A cookie is a small data file placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit certain websites.  A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited.

A web bug is a graphic on a web page or email that gathers information about the computers used to view the web page or email.  A web bug can collect your computer’s IP address and the time you viewed the website or email.

Some parts of Allegis Group’s websites use cookies and web bugs to track user traffic patterns on the Allegis Group sites.  Allegis Group does this tracking in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.

If you prefer not to receive cookies or web bugs while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies or web bugs and refuse them when your browser alerts you to their presence. 

You can also refuse all cookies and web bugs by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of Allegis Group websites if you do so.  You do not need to have cookies turned on to use/navigate through many parts of Allegis Group websites, except that access to certain Allegis Group Web pages require a login and password.

You can find information on popular browsers and how to adjust your cookie preferences at the following websites:

**Microsoft Internet Explorer:** [http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm](http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm)

**Mozilla Firefox:**[ http://www.mozilla.org/projects/security/pki/psm/help_21/using_priv_help.html](http://www.mozilla.org/projects/security/pki/psm/help_21/using_priv_help.html)

**Google Chrome:**<https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416>

**Apple Safari** :  Blocks cookies by default and accepts cookies only from your current domain.  To change, click Safari, Preferences, Security, and choose your preference.

For more information on the types of cookies which are used on the Allegis Group websites, please see our cookie statement, which is available on each of our websites. 

Back to the Top

## Sharing Your Personal Information within Allegis

Allegis Group may disclose your personal information to any affiliate within Allegis Group for use in accordance with this Privacy Statement.  This includes our subsidiaries, affiliates and our ultimate holding company. 

This sharing of personal information with Allegis Group affiliates may include combining the personal information gathered by certain Allegis Group Sites with information independently gathered on other Allegis Group Sites as well as information gathered offline into one or more database(s) useable by Allegis Group, including all of its affiliates.  Again, this combined information will only ever be used for the purposes disclosed within this Privacy Statement.

Back to the Top

## Sharing Your Personal Information with Third Parties

Allegis Group may share and disclose personal information about you with the following types of third parties and in the following circumstances:

  * **_Potential employers or potential customers_** _  - ** ** We may share your personal information if you are a job seeker with a customer for the purpose of providing the Allegis Services (such as staffing and recruiting services, or search, workforce management or talent advisory services)_ _._

_In connection with the above, we may need to disclose certain data about your previous employment (such as your resume and corresponding information or to the extent permitted by law, the results of any criminal background checks or other specific employee data such SSN/National ID) with that customer or other service providers or agents acting on our behalf to facilitate and enable the potential placement or employment. To the extent you are employed by a customer of Allegis Group through our search, workforce management or talent advisory services, the Allegis Group customer will process such personal information in accordance with its own policies and procedures.  _

  * **_Compliance with laws_** _  \- We may disclose personal information to a third party where we are legally required to do so in order to respond to or comply with any applicable law, regulation, subpoenas, court orders, legal process or government requests, including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements._

  * **_Vendors, consultants and other service providers_** _  \- We use third party vendors, consultants and other service providers to assist us in providing the Allegis Services, including to support us in areas such as recruiting and reviewing responses to job advertisements, managing résumé/CV data, IT platform management or support services, infrastructure and application services, marketing, data analytics, skills and assessments training, occupational health and safety screening, and drug and background screening. In providing these services on behalf of Allegis Group, it may be necessary for us to provide these third parties with access to your personal information.  _

_In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of individuals resident in the EEA or Switzerland received pursuant to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield or the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, Allegis Group is potentially liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if our agents process your personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.  _

  * **_Business transfers  _** _\- Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, Allegis Group decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses. Such a transaction may involve, in accordance with applicable law, the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is Allegis Group’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions._

  * **_Vital interests and legal rights_** _  \- We may collect and possibly share personal information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Allegis Group’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, including without limitation to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We also may disclose your personal information to third parties when we choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims._

  * **_With your consent_** _  \- We may disclose your personal information for other purposes with your consent. _

Your personal information is never sold, rented or leased to any external company, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

Back to the Top

## International Data Transfers

As a global company, we may transfer personal information to Allegis Group companies and third parties located in the United States and in other countries that may be outside your country of residence for storage and processing in order to provide the Allegis Services. These countries may not necessarily have data protection laws as comprehensive as those in your country or residence. We will however protect your personal information in accordance with this Policy and applicable law wherever it is processed..  

Back to the Top

## 

## EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework

For personal information we receive from the EEA, Allegis Group, Inc. and its US controlled subsidiary companies (for a full list of the US controlled subsidiary companies, click here) have certified their compliance to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries.  

We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Framework Principles of:  Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability when processing personal information from the EEA in the U.S. 

If there is a conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To access the Privacy Shield List and to find details of our certification, please visit:   [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). 

Allegis Group is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) with regards to our compliance with the Privacy Shield. 

Residents of the EEA who believe that their information has not been processed in compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles may raise their complaints in a number of ways: 

(1) You can contact us directly using the contact details provided below and we will respond to your complaint within 45 days of receipt. 

Allegis Group, Inc.

7301 Parkway Drive, 5th Floor

Hanover, MD 21076

ATTN:  Privacy Officer

Or if you are resident in the EEA:

Allegis Group Limited

c/o Legal Department

OTV House East Wing

Wokingham Road

Bracknell

Berkshire

RG42 ING

ATTN:  Legal Team

(2) We have also committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Privacy Shield, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus (" **BBB"** ). The BBB is a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint.  

(3)  Further, the European data protection authorities (DPA) may refer your complaint to the US Department of Commerce or the Federal Trade Commission for further investigation.

(4)  Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through the above methods, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration process option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.  To find out more about the Privacy Shield's binding arbitration scheme please see [www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield](http://www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield).    

## Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework Safe Harbor Framework

For personal information we receive from Switzerland, Allegis Group, Inc. and its US controlled subsidiary companies (for a full list of the US controlled subsidiary companies, click here ) have certified their compliance to the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from Switzerland to the United States. 

We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Framework Principles of:  Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability when processing personal information from Switzerland in the U.S. 

If there is a conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To access the Privacy Shield List and to find details of our certification, please visit:   [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). 

Allegis Group is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) with regards to our compliance with the Privacy Shield. 

Residents of Switzerland who believe that their information has not been processed in compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles may raise their complaints in a number of ways: 

(1) You can contact us directly using the contact details provided below and we will respond to your complaint within 45 days of receipt. 

Allegis Group, Inc.

7301 Parkway Drive, 5th Floor

Hanover, MD 21076

ATTN:  Privacy Officer

Or if you are resident in Switzerland:

Allegis Group Limited

c/o Legal Department

OTV House East Wing

Wokingham Road

Bracknell

Berkshire

RG42 ING

ATTN:  Legal Team

(2) We have also committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Privacy Shield, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus (" **BBB"** ). The BBB is a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint.  

(3)  Further, the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner may refer your complaint to the US Department of Commerce or the Federal Trade Commission for further investigation.

(4)  Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through the above methods, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration process option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.  To find out more about the Privacy Shield's binding arbitration scheme please see [www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield](http://www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield)

Back to the Top

## Your Privacy Rights

In some regions (like the European Economic Area and Switzerland), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws, which include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information

If you would like to exercise any of the above rights, please contact [privacyofficer@allegisgroup.com](mailto:privacyofficer@allegisgroup.com) (if you are a non-EEA resident) or [privacyofficerEU@allegisgroup.co.uk](mailto:privacyofficerEU@allegisgroup.co.uk) (if you are resident in the EEA or Switzerland) so that we may assess your request and determine, under applicable law, whether we are in position to comply with your request. 

To protect your privacy and security, we may take steps to verify your identity, such as a password and user ID, before granting access to data. If you are resident in the EEA or Switzerland, we will process any access request you make in accordance with our commitments under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield or the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield.

## Your Choices:

**Cookies and other similar technologies** : For information about how to disable selected cookies and other similar tracking technologies from collecting information on the Allegis Services to third party properties, please see the Section headed "Cookies and Online Tracking".

**Marketing Communications:** Where it is in accordance with your marketing preferences, we may periodically send you updates via e-mail about promotional opportunities or services we think may interest you, such as jobs in our database that match your selection criteria. 

You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications by clicking "Unsubscribe" in any e-mail communications we send you.  At the point where we request personal information about you, our Sites also give you the opportunity to decide which communications you receive.

Back to the Top

## Security of Your Personal Information

Allegis Group is committed to protecting the personal information you share with us.  Allegis Group uses appropriate physical, technical, organizational and administrative security measures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized or unlawful access, use or disclosure, and from accidental loss, destruction or damage. 

Allegis Group supports online security using secure server technology because we want your data to be safe.  We use state-of-the-art security arrangements and facilities on our Sites and through the Allegis Services to maintain data security. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet cannot be guaranteed 100% completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information that is transferred over the internet. 

If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of your account has been compromised), please immediately notify us in accordance with the "Contact Us" section below.

Back to the Top

## Children's Privacy

This site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13.  Allegis Group does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.  If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. 

Back to the Top

## Links to Other Sites and Public Forums

Allegis Group Sites may contain links to other sites for your convenience and information.  If you access those links, you will leave the Allegis Group Site.  Allegis Group does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from Allegis Group’s practices.  Allegis Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites outside of Allegis Group.  The personal information you choose to provide or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by this Policy.  We encourage you to review the policy of such third parties  before submitting your personal information.

Allegis Group may make message boards, news groups, and/or public forums available to users on its Sites.  Any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information that may be accessed by third parties; therefore, you should use caution before deciding to disclose any personal information in these forums. 

Back to the Top

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Policy or if you wish to exercise Your Privacy Rights please contact:

Allegis Group, Inc.

7301 Parkway Drive, 5th Floor

Hanover, MD 21076

ATTN:  Privacy Officer

Or if you are resident in the EEA or Switzerland:

Allegis Group Limited

c/o Legal Department

OTV House East Wing

Wokingham Road

Bracknell

Berkshire

RG42 ING

ATTN:  Legal Team

Back to the Top

##  

## Changes to this Policy

If we change this Policy, we will post the revised Policy on our Sites, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our Policy, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page. To view previous versions of the Policy, [click here](http://www.allegisgroup.com/Privacy-Previous/).  We will update the "Effective Date" at the top of this page to indicate the date from which any changes take effect.

Back to the Top

## Additional Notices

Some Allegis Services may have additional privacy notices about how such websites, products and services process personal information.   For example, a supplemental Privacy Policy for MarketSource is provided at the bottom of this Policy.

In addition, sometimes Allegis Group acts as a data processor, for example when processing personal information it receives from one of its customers as part of its workforce management or talent advisory services.  Any time that Allegis Group acts as a data processor, it will process personal information according to the contractual obligations it has with the applicable data controller.  To the extent Allegis Group receives requests from individuals regarding the processing of their personal information by Allegis Group, it will refer them to and coordinate with the appropriate data controller. 

## Additional Information That Applies to MarketSource Customers

MarketSource works closely with a variety of retailer businesses (" **MarketSource** **Customers** ") to help them market and sell products and services to their end customers (" **MarketSource End Customers"** ). 

In connection with the retailer services and solutions that MarketSource provides to MarketSource Customers, MarketSource may collect and process personal information (like contact information, transaction history, marketing preferences or geographic location information) about MarketSource End Customers on behalf of MarketSource Customers for the following purposes: 

  * To  process direct sales and transactions; and

  * For MarketSource Customer's business purposes, such as: 

    * Data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention; 
    * Developing new products, services and offerings; 
    * Enhancing, improving or modifying  MarktSource Customers’ merchandising, Sites, products and/or services; 
    * Identifying usage or purchase trends; 
    * Determining  and evaluating the effectiveness of a MarketSource Customer's engagement with its MarketSource End Customers and related promotional campaigns; and 
    * Operating and expanding their business activities. 

The MarketSource Customer is the data controller of any personal information about MarketSource End Customers.  As such, a MarketSource End Customer who wishes access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his or her query to the relevant MarketSource Customer.  MarketSource will assist any MarketSource Customer as necessary to comply with any MarketSource End Customer data subject request. 

© Allegis Group, Inc., 2017.  All rights reserved.

## Allegis Group Online Privacy Statement

_Effective Date: 2017_

Allegis Group and its group companies, click here, (collectively, " **Allegis Group** ", or " **we"** ) are committed to safeguarding your privacy. In this Privacy & Cookie Policy (" **Policy** ") we explain to you what information we may collect, use, share and store about you, and the choices and rights that are available to you.  If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us using the contact details provided below. 

We participate in and comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Economic Area (" **EEA** ") member countries and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. You can find out more about our Privacy Shield commitment's below, click here.

## About Allegis Group

##  

Through our network of specialized operating companies, Allegis Group partners with organizations across the globe to optimize talent attraction and retention— while simultaneously providing individuals with significant opportunities to realize their professional aspirations and achieve personal success.  We partner with clients to help them achieve their talent strategies and business goals, and we partner with potential candidates about their career aspirations.  

Using our industry expertise we’ve developed a full suite of talent solutions — from talent acquisition services to fully-outsourced workforce management offerings.  To learn more about the details of our services offerings, please click here.

• Staffing and recruiting services for technical, professional, and industrial positions through Aerotek, as well as managed engineering services via EASi.

• Staffing and recruiting services for risk and compliance, operations, business and organizational change, finance, and management consultancy positions via Aston Carter.

• Legal search, recruiting, and flexible workforce services for lawyers and legal professionals through Major, Lindsey & Africa and MLA-Solutions Practice Group.

• Executive search services across an entire organization, including board of directors, C-suite, executive and senior VPs, and directors through Allegis Partners.

• An online job board and resource for job seekers with disabilities and employers looking to hire in the U.S. via Getting Hired.

• IT staffing solutions, IT talent management expertise, as well as managed, project-based, and outsourced IT services via TEKsystems Global Services

• A proven alternative to outsourced sales, providing customized sales solutions for retail and B2B customers through MarketSource.

• Permanent and contingent workforce management solutions, talent advisory services, and integrated talent solutions through Allegis Global Solutions.

## When this Policy Applies

This Policy applies to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information:

(i)       through our website(s) and related applications and content that link or refer to this Policy (including the Allegis Group websites listed here: Allegis Group websites); and Allegis computer or mobile software applications (“ **apps** ”) and content made available to you) (collectively the “ **Sites** ”); 

(ii)      in connection with any of our events or sales, marketing, advertising and recruitment activities or in the course of providing other Allegis Group services to you (collectively with the Sites, the " **Allegis Services** "); and

(iii)      when receiving services from you.

This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of third parties that Allegis Group does not own or control.

Back to the Top

**What is in this Policy?**

_Click on one of the links below to jump to a specific section:_

_Collection of Personal Information  
Use of Personal Information  
Cookies and Online Tracking  
Sharing Your Personal Information within Allegis  
Sharing Your Personal Information with Third Parties  
International Data Transfers  
EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework  
Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework Safe Harbor Framework  
Your Privacy Rights  
Security of Your Personal Information  
Children’s Privacy  
Links to Other Sites and Public Forums  
Contacting Us  
Changes to this Policy  
Additional Notices  
Additional Information That Applies to MarketSource Customers_

## Collection of Personal Information

Allegis Group collects and maintains personal information from the following categories of individuals:

  * **Visitors:** individuals who visit or use our Site(s) or any other Allegis Services, so that we can provide them with the Site(s) or Allegis Services they require;

  * **Job seekers** : individuals that apply for job opportunities with Allegis Group to fill our internal positions or as part of our staffing and recruiting services or Allegis Group’s customers through our search, workforce management or talent advisory services (in each case, whether such applications are made online or offline) **;**

  * **Customers, vendors, service providers and other suppliers** : employees, representatives and/or agents of our customers, service providers, vendors and other suppliers with whom we have a business relationship and/or manage on behalf of our customers. 

If you submit any personal information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the Allegis Services, you confirm that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Policy. 

**The types of information we collect include the following:**

  * **Information submitted to us:** Allegis Group collects personal information that individuals provide to us through Allegis Services, such as when they visit one of our Sites, post on our forums or blogs, sign up for an Allegis account to access certain Allegis Services (like an Allegis Group job board or our Communities Site) or if they subscribe to our marketing or register for an Allegis Group event or webinar or otherwise contact us.  We may also collect personal information from individuals’ offline, for example when individuals provide information to us by telephone or in person at events or at one of our recruitment offices.   

The types of personal information we may collect include:

    * contact information (such as name, postal address, email address and telephone number); 

    * username and password when you register on our Sites; 

    * professional information, such as your job title, department or job role; 

    * information you provide about others you would like us to contact (for example referrals or references) or information regarding your emergency contacts; 

    * resume or C.V. information, such as employment and education history, language proficiencies, security clearance information and other work-related skills, awards and honors, membership in clubs and organizations, personal interests and activities and information regarding your career interests and other qualifications for or desires regarding future employment opportunities, including information regarding desired compensation and benefits; and 

    * citizenship and work authorization status.  

Where we request information from you, we will let you know prior to collection whether the provision of the personal information we are requesting is compulsory or whether the information may be provided on a voluntary basis and the consequences of not providing the information.  ** **

  * **Information we collect automatically:** We automatically collect certain technical information from visitors to our Site(s), such as the Internet protocol (IP) address of their device, their login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platforms.  We may also automatically collect certain information about their visits to our Site(s), such as download errors experienced and length of visits to certain pages. When you download, install or use Allegis Group apps, we and our service providers may track and collect certain device related information (such as your device's unique ID) and certain app usage data (such as the date and time the app on your device accesses our servers and what information and files have been downloaded to the app based on your device ID. 

  * **Information we receive from other sources or third parties:**  We may receive or acquire information about our visitors, job seekers, customers and suppliers from third party partners (such as background check providers) or other third party sources (such as information from publically available sites (like Monster.com, CareerBuilder.com or LinkedIn)),or a job seeker’s third party reference.  

  * You may also choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by third parties like social media sites.  For example, if you register for an account to access some of our Sites (like the Communities Site), you can choose to import your LinkedIn basic profile data (such as your name, experience, location, photo and contact information). By authorizing Allegis Group to have access to this information, you agree that we may collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

** Sensitive Personal Information: **In connection with the various services we provide or if you are applying for a job opportunity with us or one of our customers, you may be asked  for types of  personal information that are viewed by some countries as sensitive personal information. Sensitive personal information includes, for example, government-issued  identification number (such as  a social security number), information relating to a person's race or ethnic origin, political opinions or religious beliefs, physical or mental health or  condition, sexual orientation, trade union  membership, genetic data and any related legal actions or the processing of biometric data for the purposes of uniquely identifying an  individual.  It also includes information about an individual's  criminal offences or convictions, as well as any other information deemed sensitive under applicable data protection  laws (collectively **"Sensitive Personal Information").  **

  * Although we aim to minimize the amount of Sensitive Personal Information we process, we may process such information in certain circumstances, such as where we are required to or permitted to do so by law (e.g. information about your racial / ethnic origin, gender and disabilities for equal opportunity monitoring or affirmative action program), or where it is necessary to provide you with a service, or if we need to perform a criminal background check, drug/alcohol test or fitness for duty testing.  If required by applicable data protection laws, we will obtain your express consent to our use of your sensitive personal information. .

## Use of Personal Information

The personal information Allegis Group collects will be used only as described in this Policy and/or in the way we specify at the time of collection.  For the most part, we collect and use personal information to effectively provide and improve the Allegis Services (such as our Sites and related staffing and recruiting services, or search, workforce management or talent advisory services)  and to comply with applicable laws and government regulations (such as,  to comply with mandatory employment, tax and insurance requirements). 

More specifically, we may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * Providing  and administering the Allegis Services and for internal operations (for example, troubleshooting, data analysis, statistical and survey purposes); 
  * Protecting the Allegis Services (for example, fraud monitoring and prevention); 
  * Responding to your communications;  
  * Complying with applicable laws and government regulations; 
  * If you are a job seeker: 
    * facilitating the recruitment, staffing or search process by helping to find job seekers a suitable assignment or job match with us or with our customers; 
    * storing information about your recruitment or other preferences; 
    * sending you e-mails and other communications about job postings that we think fit your profile, and to notify you about events, surveys, workshops and training sessions run by Allegis Group; and 
    * to interact with you on third party social networks (like LinkedIn). 
  * Gauging the number of users and usage of the Site(s), so we can plan Site bandwidth and capacity accordingly; 
  * Recognizing you when you return as a repeat visitor to our Site(s) or other online Allegis Services; 
  * Providing information on goods and services you have requested; 
  * Sending you e-mails and other promotional communications about Allegis Group marketing, advertising and promotions in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt-out of our marketing at any time (see "Your Choices" below); 
  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, services and offerings, enhancing, improving or modifying our Sites, products and services and operating and expanding our business activities; and

  * Notifying you about changes to our Site(s) or other Allegis Services.

Personal information collected online through the Allegis Services may also be supplemented with information you provide to us through other Allegis Group services , as well as other online and offline sources (such as recruitment fairs, social media platforms (like LinkedIn), trade shows, or other events) and other data appending methods (such as spot tags, tracking and cookies as referenced below).

We may also use the personal information we receive for the purposes of creating anonymized and aggregated statistics that do not reveal the specific identity of any person.

In most cases, Allegis Group will process personal information for a variety of business purposes which are in our  legitimate interests (for example, to operate its business and provide you with services you have requested), in order to enter into or perform a contract with youand/or for compliance with our legal obligations (as described above). However in some cases and always where required by applicable law, Allegis Group will seek your consent to process your personal information (including any Sensitive Personal Information).  

Back to the Top

## Cookies and Online Tracking

Allegis Group websites use "cookies" and similar technologies (like web bugs) to help personalize your online experience and for our analytics purposes. 

A cookie is a small data file placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit certain websites.  A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited.

A web bug is a graphic on a web page or email that gathers information about the computers used to view the web page or email.  A web bug can collect your computer’s IP address and the time you viewed the website or email.

Some parts of Allegis Group’s websites use cookies and web bugs to track user traffic patterns on the Allegis Group sites.  Allegis Group does this tracking in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.

If you prefer not to receive cookies or web bugs while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies or web bugs and refuse them when your browser alerts you to their presence. 

You can also refuse all cookies and web bugs by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of Allegis Group websites if you do so.  You do not need to have cookies turned on to use/navigate through many parts of Allegis Group websites, except that access to certain Allegis Group Web pages require a login and password.

You can find information on popular browsers and how to adjust your cookie preferences at the following websites:

**Microsoft Internet Explorer:** [http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm](http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm)

**Mozilla Firefox:**[ http://www.mozilla.org/projects/security/pki/psm/help_21/using_priv_help.html](http://www.mozilla.org/projects/security/pki/psm/help_21/using_priv_help.html)

**Google Chrome:**<https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416>

**Apple Safari** :  Blocks cookies by default and accepts cookies only from your current domain.  To change, click Safari, Preferences, Security, and choose your preference.

For more information on the types of cookies which are used on the Allegis Group websites, please see our cookie statement, which is available on each of our websites. 

Back to the Top

## Sharing Your Personal Information within Allegis

Allegis Group may disclose your personal information to any affiliate within Allegis Group for use in accordance with this Privacy Statement.  This includes our subsidiaries, affiliates and our ultimate holding company. 

This sharing of personal information with Allegis Group affiliates may include combining the personal information gathered by certain Allegis Group Sites with information independently gathered on other Allegis Group Sites as well as information gathered offline into one or more database(s) useable by Allegis Group, including all of its affiliates.  Again, this combined information will only ever be used for the purposes disclosed within this Privacy Statement.

Back to the Top

## Sharing Your Personal Information with Third Parties

Allegis Group may share and disclose personal information about you with the following types of third parties and in the following circumstances:

  * **_Potential employers or potential customers_** _  - ** ** We may share your personal information if you are a job seeker with a customer for the purpose of providing the Allegis Services (such as staffing and recruiting services, or search, workforce management or talent advisory services)_ _._

_In connection with the above, we may need to disclose certain data about your previous employment (such as your resume and corresponding information or to the extent permitted by law, the results of any criminal background checks or other specific employee data such SSN/National ID) with that customer or other service providers or agents acting on our behalf to facilitate and enable the potential placement or employment. To the extent you are employed by a customer of Allegis Group through our search, workforce management or talent advisory services, the Allegis Group customer will process such personal information in accordance with its own policies and procedures.  _

  * **_Compliance with laws_** _  \- We may disclose personal information to a third party where we are legally required to do so in order to respond to or comply with any applicable law, regulation, subpoenas, court orders, legal process or government requests, including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements._

  * **_Vendors, consultants and other service providers_** _  \- We use third party vendors, consultants and other service providers to assist us in providing the Allegis Services, including to support us in areas such as recruiting and reviewing responses to job advertisements, managing résumé/CV data, IT platform management or support services, infrastructure and application services, marketing, data analytics, skills and assessments training, occupational health and safety screening, and drug and background screening. In providing these services on behalf of Allegis Group, it may be necessary for us to provide these third parties with access to your personal information.  _

_In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of individuals resident in the EEA or Switzerland received pursuant to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield or the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, Allegis Group is potentially liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if our agents process your personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.  _

  * **_Business transfers  _** _\- Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, Allegis Group decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses. Such a transaction may involve, in accordance with applicable law, the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is Allegis Group’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions._

  * **_Vital interests and legal rights_** _  \- We may collect and possibly share personal information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Allegis Group’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, including without limitation to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We also may disclose your personal information to third parties when we choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims._

  * **_With your consent_** _  \- We may disclose your personal information for other purposes with your consent. _

Your personal information is never sold, rented or leased to any external company, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

Back to the Top

## International Data Transfers

As a global company, we may transfer personal information to Allegis Group companies and third parties located in the United States and in other countries that may be outside your country of residence for storage and processing in order to provide the Allegis Services. These countries may not necessarily have data protection laws as comprehensive as those in your country or residence. We will however protect your personal information in accordance with this Policy and applicable law wherever it is processed..  

Back to the Top

## 

## EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework

For personal information we receive from the EEA, Allegis Group, Inc. and its US controlled subsidiary companies (for a full list of the US controlled subsidiary companies, click here) have certified their compliance to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries.  

We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Framework Principles of:  Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability when processing personal information from the EEA in the U.S. 

If there is a conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To access the Privacy Shield List and to find details of our certification, please visit:   [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). 

Allegis Group is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) with regards to our compliance with the Privacy Shield. 

Residents of the EEA who believe that their information has not been processed in compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles may raise their complaints in a number of ways: 

(1) You can contact us directly using the contact details provided below and we will respond to your complaint within 45 days of receipt. 

Allegis Group, Inc.

7301 Parkway Drive, 5th Floor

Hanover, MD 21076

ATTN:  Privacy Officer

Or if you are resident in the EEA:

Allegis Group Limited

c/o Legal Department

OTV House East Wing

Wokingham Road

Bracknell

Berkshire

RG42 ING

ATTN:  Legal Team

(2) We have also committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Privacy Shield, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus (" **BBB"** ). The BBB is a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint.  

(3)  Further, the European data protection authorities (DPA) may refer your complaint to the US Department of Commerce or the Federal Trade Commission for further investigation.

(4)  Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through the above methods, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration process option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.  To find out more about the Privacy Shield's binding arbitration scheme please see [www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield](http://www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield).    

## Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework Safe Harbor Framework

For personal information we receive from Switzerland, Allegis Group, Inc. and its US controlled subsidiary companies (for a full list of the US controlled subsidiary companies, click here ) have certified their compliance to the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from Switzerland to the United States. 

We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Framework Principles of:  Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability when processing personal information from Switzerland in the U.S. 

If there is a conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To access the Privacy Shield List and to find details of our certification, please visit:   [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). 

Allegis Group is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) with regards to our compliance with the Privacy Shield. 

Residents of Switzerland who believe that their information has not been processed in compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles may raise their complaints in a number of ways: 

(1) You can contact us directly using the contact details provided below and we will respond to your complaint within 45 days of receipt. 

Allegis Group, Inc.

7301 Parkway Drive, 5th Floor

Hanover, MD 21076

ATTN:  Privacy Officer

Or if you are resident in Switzerland:

Allegis Group Limited

c/o Legal Department

OTV House East Wing

Wokingham Road

Bracknell

Berkshire

RG42 ING

ATTN:  Legal Team

(2) We have also committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Privacy Shield, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus (" **BBB"** ). The BBB is a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint.  

(3)  Further, the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner may refer your complaint to the US Department of Commerce or the Federal Trade Commission for further investigation.

(4)  Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through the above methods, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration process option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.  To find out more about the Privacy Shield's binding arbitration scheme please see [www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield](http://www.privacyshield.gob/article?id=My-Rights-under-Privacy-Shield)

Back to the Top

## Your Privacy Rights

In some regions (like the European Economic Area and Switzerland), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws, which include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information

If you would like to exercise any of the above rights, please contact [privacyofficer@allegisgroup.com](mailto:privacyofficer@allegisgroup.com) (if you are a non-EEA resident) or [privacyofficerEU@allegisgroup.co.uk](mailto:privacyofficerEU@allegisgroup.co.uk) (if you are resident in the EEA or Switzerland) so that we may assess your request and determine, under applicable law, whether we are in position to comply with your request. 

To protect your privacy and security, we may take steps to verify your identity, such as a password and user ID, before granting access to data. If you are resident in the EEA or Switzerland, we will process any access request you make in accordance with our commitments under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield or the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield.

## Your Choices:

**Cookies and other similar technologies** : For information about how to disable selected cookies and other similar tracking technologies from collecting information on the Allegis Services to third party properties, please see the Section headed "Cookies and Online Tracking".

**Marketing Communications:** Where it is in accordance with your marketing preferences, we may periodically send you updates via e-mail about promotional opportunities or services we think may interest you, such as jobs in our database that match your selection criteria. 

You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications by clicking "Unsubscribe" in any e-mail communications we send you.  At the point where we request personal information about you, our Sites also give you the opportunity to decide which communications you receive.

Back to the Top

## Security of Your Personal Information

Allegis Group is committed to protecting the personal information you share with us.  Allegis Group uses appropriate physical, technical, organizational and administrative security measures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized or unlawful access, use or disclosure, and from accidental loss, destruction or damage. 

Allegis Group supports online security using secure server technology because we want your data to be safe.  We use state-of-the-art security arrangements and facilities on our Sites and through the Allegis Services to maintain data security. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet cannot be guaranteed 100% completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information that is transferred over the internet. 

If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of your account has been compromised), please immediately notify us in accordance with the "Contact Us" section below.

Back to the Top

## Children's Privacy

This site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13.  Allegis Group does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.  If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. 

Back to the Top

## Links to Other Sites and Public Forums

Allegis Group Sites may contain links to other sites for your convenience and information.  If you access those links, you will leave the Allegis Group Site.  Allegis Group does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from Allegis Group’s practices.  Allegis Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites outside of Allegis Group.  The personal information you choose to provide or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by this Policy.  We encourage you to review the policy of such third parties  before submitting your personal information.

Allegis Group may make message boards, news groups, and/or public forums available to users on its Sites.  Any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information that may be accessed by third parties; therefore, you should use caution before deciding to disclose any personal information in these forums. 

Back to the Top

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Policy or if you wish to exercise Your Privacy Rights please contact:

Allegis Group, Inc.

7301 Parkway Drive, 5th Floor

Hanover, MD 21076

ATTN:  Privacy Officer

Or if you are resident in the EEA or Switzerland:

Allegis Group Limited

c/o Legal Department

OTV House East Wing

Wokingham Road

Bracknell

Berkshire

RG42 ING

ATTN:  Legal Team

Back to the Top

##  

## Changes to this Policy

If we change this Policy, we will post the revised Policy on our Sites, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our Policy, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page. To view previous versions of the Policy, [click here](http://www.allegisgroup.com/Privacy-Previous/).  We will update the "Effective Date" at the top of this page to indicate the date from which any changes take effect.

Back to the Top

## Additional Notices

Some Allegis Services may have additional privacy notices about how such websites, products and services process personal information.   For example, a supplemental Privacy Policy for MarketSource is provided at the bottom of this Policy.

In addition, sometimes Allegis Group acts as a data processor, for example when processing personal information it receives from one of its customers as part of its workforce management or talent advisory services.  Any time that Allegis Group acts as a data processor, it will process personal information according to the contractual obligations it has with the applicable data controller.  To the extent Allegis Group receives requests from individuals regarding the processing of their personal information by Allegis Group, it will refer them to and coordinate with the appropriate data controller. 

## Additional Information That Applies to MarketSource Customers

MarketSource works closely with a variety of retailer businesses (" **MarketSource** **Customers** ") to help them market and sell products and services to their end customers (" **MarketSource End Customers"** ). 

In connection with the retailer services and solutions that MarketSource provides to MarketSource Customers, MarketSource may collect and process personal information (like contact information, transaction history, marketing preferences or geographic location information) about MarketSource End Customers on behalf of MarketSource Customers for the following purposes: 

  * To  process direct sales and transactions; and

  * For MarketSource Customer's business purposes, such as: 

    * Data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention; 
    * Developing new products, services and offerings; 
    * Enhancing, improving or modifying  MarktSource Customers’ merchandising, Sites, products and/or services; 
    * Identifying usage or purchase trends; 
    * Determining  and evaluating the effectiveness of a MarketSource Customer's engagement with its MarketSource End Customers and related promotional campaigns; and 
    * Operating and expanding their business activities. 

The MarketSource Customer is the data controller of any personal information about MarketSource End Customers.  As such, a MarketSource End Customer who wishes access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his or her query to the relevant MarketSource Customer.  MarketSource will assist any MarketSource Customer as necessary to comply with any MarketSource End Customer data subject request. 

© Allegis Group, Inc., 2017.  All rights reserved.
